mgincomegroup.com 2013-03-02

# mgincomegroup.com | Flow with the profit

|  |   |  |    
---|---|---|---  
  
Privacy **Policy**   
Our **Policies**  
---  
| 

mgincomegroup.com is a professional forex trading company that not only adheres to statutory guidelines on customer’s privacy, but also to ethical guidelines. In everything that we do, we operate in such a way as to guarantee the safety of your personal information and your peace of mind.

This privacy policy describes the way in which we gather, store, and use your private information. This private information includes details such as your name, email address, physical address and so on. In this document, all these will henceforth be referred to as “information.”   
  
---  
  
Information Gathering  
  
Why We Gather

We gather information for the following reasons:

  1. In order to comply with statutory obligations
  2. To protect your account from unlawful entry
  3. In order to be able to transact with you

When We Gather

  1. During the registration process when you open an account
  2. When you make transactions such as deposits and withdrawals

How We Gather

The main source of the personal information that we need comes from you. You are required to provide us with information that is accurate. Some of the information that you’ll to provide is mandatory while some is optional. We also gather information when you respond to queries, ask questions, or seek support services.

Use of Information

The information that we gather is used to communicate with you, verify your account, and meet statutory requirements. 

We also use the information gathered to help your browsing experience become better and come up with creative ways of meeting your unique needs.

Deactivated Accounts

In case you deactivate your account ( when your deposit expired ), we’ll keep your information with us in order to comply with statutory requirements. We may also use the information to contact you when we see there’s need to share some information.  

Sharing Information

At mgincomegroup.com, we’ve adopted a strict privacy policy that is designed to protect your personal information from misuse. We do not share your information with any third party unless: 

  * When required to fulfill statutory obligations or court directions. 
  * In order to protect you from fraud, or the carrying out of illegal transactions through your account
  * Communicating to other service providers who deal with opening, operating and servicing your account. 

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_  
  
mgincomegroup.com reserves the right to revise, modify, amend and/or change this policy at any time we deem fit. Any time this happens, we’ll notify you through our website and through email.

Got Questions?

Do you have any questions, comments, or suggestions regarding our privacy policy? We’d love to hear from you. Get in touch with us through mgincomegroup.com
